Guide to the President's Council of Cornell Women records, 1990-2015.
President's Council of Cornell Women records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
President's Council of Cornell Women records, 1990-2015.
41-9-3922
President's Council of Cornell Women
2.3 cubic feet.
Computer media, photographs, research material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes meeting minutes, bylaws, membership information, publicity photographs, DVDs, CDs and videotapes.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
The President's Council of Cornell Women (PCCW) was founded in 1990 by former President Frank Rhodes. It is a group of alumnae working to enhance the involvement of women students, faculty, staff, and alumnae as leaders within Cornell University and its many communities.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes meeting minutes, bylaws, membership information, publicity photographs, DVDs, CDs and videotapes.
SUBJECTS
Names:
President's Council of Cornell Women; Cornell University -- Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University -- Faculty.; Cornell University.
Subjects:
Women -- New York (State) -- Ithaca -- Societies and clubs.; Women college students.
Places:
Tompkins County (N.Y.) -- Social life and customs.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Videotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Constitution and Bylaws, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Constitution and Bylaws, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Steering Committee, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Steering Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Steering Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Steering Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Steering Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Steering Committee, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Steering Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Steering Committee, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Steering Committee, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Steering Committee, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Steering Committee, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Steering Committee, 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Annual Meeting, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Annual Meeting, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Annual Meeting, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Annual Meeting, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Annual Meeting, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Annual Meeting, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Annual Meeting, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Annual Meeting, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Annual Meeting, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Annual Meeting, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Annual Meeting, 2011-2013 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Communication, Public Relations and Visibility, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Development, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Development, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Development, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Development, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Development, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Development, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Diversity/Advance Task Force, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Diversity/Advance Task Force, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Grants, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Grants, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Grants, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Grants, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Grants, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Grants, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Grants, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Grants, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Grants, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Grants, 2009-2011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Grants, 2011-2013 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Membership, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Membership, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Membership, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Membership, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Membership, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Membership, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Membership, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Membership, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Membership, 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Transitions, 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- PCCW Task Force, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- PCCW Task Force, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Time Line task Force, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Photographs, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Photographs, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Photographs, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Photographs, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Photographs, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Photographs, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Photographs, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Photographs, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Photographs, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Photographs, 2006-2007 (Box 3)
- Photographs on CD's and DVD's, 2007-2013 (Box 3)
- "At-A-Glance" program, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Fall Meeting, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- President Skorton letter, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 25th Anniversary Annual Meeting, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 25th Anniversary poster, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Includes CD-2606 - contains a PDF of the original poster, which was 18" x 84"